Truth is the only justice.
Frontera is a western, drama film directed by Michael Berry.
After crossing the border illegally for work, Miguel, a hard-working father and devoted
husband, finds himself wrongfully accused of murdering a former sheriff’s wife.
After learning of his imprisonment, Miguel’s pregnant wife tries to come to his aid
and lands in the hands of corrupt coyotes who hold her for ransom.
Dissatisfied with the police department’s investigation, the former sheriff tries to uncover the truth about his wife’s
death and discovers disturbing evidence that will destroy one family’s future, or tear another’s apart.
Roy, played by Ed Harris.
Paulina, played by Eva Longoria.
Miguel, played by Michael Peña.
Olivia, played by Amy Madigan.
ICE Guard, played by Kristen DeVore Rakes.
Sean, played by Seth Adkins.
Frontera is a 2014 American Western drama film directed by Michael Berry.
The film spotlights illegal immigration from various perspectives, and
stars Ed Harris, Michael Peña, Eva Longoria and Amy Madigan.
The tone is dark and emotional.